

Kamil Dróżdż

Front-end Developer

My Contact

1 +48 570728479

Warsaw

https://kamildrozdz.pl

in LinkedIn

Github

Skills

React

Js JavaScript

♠ Git

GitHub

∃ HTML(Metodology BEM)

CSS(SASS, Tailwind)

RWD

SEO SEO

WordPress

Achievements

React Basics, Coursera

November 2022

Programming with JavaScript , Coursera
October 2022

JavaScript Algorithms and Data Structures, FreeCodeCamp

October 2022

Certyficate EF SET™, The EF Standard English Test (EF SET)

October 2022

Course basic Javascript, Udemy

September 2022

Experience

Performer at Polski Standard, Warsaw

March 2018 - current

- Creating offers,
- Team management,
- Creating a website in Wordpress,
- · Modernizing and updating the website,
- · Acquiring orders,
- · Performing orders and picking up with the customer,
- · Keeping in touch with customers,
- · Accounting,
- · Work schedule,
- · Negotiations and discussions with clients.

Health and safety worker at Twence B.V, Hengelo

August 2017 - April 2018

- Knowledge of labor law and OHS provisions,
- · Responsibility for colleagues during the joint work,
- · Working under time pressure,
- · Keeping the workplace clean,
- · Team management, supervision over entrusted tasks.

Education Background

2013 - 2017

Technical School in Lipno, Lipno Education level: secondary

Specialization: Construction Technician 2019–2021

Non-public General Secondary School for Adults in Zielonka, Zielonka Education level: secondary

Specialization: Health and Safety

About me

My goal is to gain experience in programming, develop organizational and future managerial skills.

I want to improve towards Front-end programming, learn from the best, broaden my horizons through courses, trainings, guides, but also by doing my own projects, under the watchful eye of experienced programmers.

My story began with the desire to create a website based on Wordpress. After starting it, I felt unsatisfied. I found that I wanted more interference in its appearance than just using someone else's templates. Independent programming, design and the entire web development process give me great joy and I would like to develop further.

Therefore, I am very interested in working permanently in a company with extensive programming experience.

I hereby consent to my personal data being processed by for the purpose of considering my application for the vacancy I hereby consent to my personal data being processed by for the purpose of future recrutations purposes